Encounters are mysterious! But cases are even more so!
لقاءات البشر مغلّفة بالغموض، والقضايا تلفّها طبقات أكثر حتّى
I'm so glad to have met you!
!أنا مسرورٌ حقّاً لكوني معك
What might today's wine taste like?
كيف سيكون مذاق نبيذ اليوم؟
Don't judge something by its name!
!لا تحكم على شيءٍ من اسمه
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
I don't get it.
لا أفهم
Why were we invited, too?
لمَ تمّت دعوتنا نحن أيضاً؟
How should I know?
لا أدري
You don't really care?
لستَ مهتمّاً؟
Of course not!
!بالطبع لا
Ichikawa Kotaro may be president of Ichikawa Industries now,
قد يكون إيتشيكاوا كوتارو رئيس ،إيتشيكاوا للصناعات الآن
Ichikawa Industries
إيتشيكاوا للصناعات
but he's also a deceitful jerk.
لكنّه وغدٌ مخادع أيضاً
I doubt he has honest work for me.
سيكون طلب عمل غير محترم بالتأكيد
Then why don't you say no?
لمَ لا ترفضه إذاً؟
Grownups have grownup circumstances to take care of!
!للبالغين ظروفهم
Yeah, that's true.
بالفعل
He hasn't had any work at all for a long time now.
لم يتلقَّ أيّ عمل لوقتٍ طويل
Mori-sama, yes?
موري-ساما، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
أجل
We've been expecting you.
كنّا بانتظارك
Please come in.
تفضّل
Is there a party going on?
أتوجد حفلةٌ الآن؟
The president has a family meeting every year on his birthday.
يقيم الرئيس اجتماعاً عائليّاً كلّ عام على عيد ميلاده
Mori-sama is here to see you.
أتى موري-ساما لمقابلتك
Enter.
ادخل
This is Ichikawa, the head of the house.
هذا إيتشيكاوا، سيّد المنزل
Thank you for coming.
شكراً على قدومك
Just so you know, I haven't decided to help you just yet.
ليكن في علمك، لم أقرّر قبول طلبك بعد
Imamura.
إيمامورا
Imamura Toshiaki (55) Ichikawa family butler
(إيمامورا توشياكي (55 كبير خدم عائلة إيتشيكاوا
100,000 yen?!
!مئة ألف ينّ؟
You must take the great Mori Kogoro for a cheap joke!
لا تسترخص خدمات المتحرّي !العظيم موري كوغورو
Wait, mister.
يا عمّ
What?
ماذا؟
It isn't 100,000 yen.
ليست مئة ألف
See?
انظر
One, ten, hundred, thousand, ten thousand, hundred thousand--
،آحاد، عشرات، مئات، آحاد ألوف ...عشرات ألوف، مئات ألوف
A-A million yen?!
!مـ-مليون ينّ؟
I've prepared another million yen
حضّرت مليون ينّ أخرى
Ichikawa Kotaro President of Ichikawa Industries
(إيتشيكاوا كوتارو (65 رئيس إيتشيكاوا للصناعة
for you if your job is successful.
إذا أتممت عملك بنجاح
So, how can I help you?
إذاً، كيف أخدمك؟
Geez...
...يا إلهي
My two daughters will be in attendance at today's family meeting.
ستحضر ابنتاي اجتماع اليوم العائليّ
I want you to watch what they do and what they try to do.
أريدك أن تراقب ما الذي ستفعلانه وما الذي ستحاولان فعله
Huh?
ماذا؟
Umm, should I leave?
المعذرة، هل أغادر؟
No, it's fine. You can explain my condition to them.
كلا، لا داعي، يمكنك شرح حالتي له
Right.
حاضر
If he continues to push himself,
(أوكانو هيتوشي (30 طبيب كوتارو الخاص
Okano Hitoshi (30) Kotaro's physician
،إذا واصل الضغط على نفسه
there's no guarantee he'll live.
فلا ضمان لبقائه على قيد الحياة
So I'm thinking of retiring now, but I need to decide on a successor.
لذا أفكّر بالتقاعد قريباً، لكن عليّ تحديد خليفة
It'd be one of your daughters, right?
ستكون إحدى ابنتيك، صحيح؟
Not necessarily.
ليس بالضرورة
I have no intention of sharing my fortune with uncouth vultures,
،لا نيّة لديّ بمشاركة ثروتي مع جشعين غير محترمين
which may include my children.
ولو كانوا أبنائي
Even so, inheritances are subject to legally-secured portions.
مع ذلك، هناك حصص مفروضة قانونياً في الميراث
Your children would still get a percent of it, no matter what.
ستتلقّى ابنتاك حصّتيهما مهما كان الأمر
But not if there's an issue with who it's going to.
لكن ألا يختلف الموضوع إن كنت أملك مشكلة مع من سينالها؟
Issue?
مشكلة؟
Something's going to happen. Something. I can feel it.
هناك شيءٌ ما، بل أستشعر حصول شيءٍ بالتأكيد
Something?
شيء؟
I've told everyone you're a friend, and that you're with your family.
أخبرتُ الجميع أنّك صديقي، ومن العائلة
Be careful not to be found out as you do your work.
لكن حاذر ألا يكشفوك في عملك
Right...
حسناً
So Ran and I are camouflage?
أي أنّي وران مجرّد غطاء تمويه؟
Still, what a horrible guy this is.
مع ذلك، يا للمُسنّ البغيض
Cheers!
!نخبك
Mori-sama. Over there is Kazue-san, the eldest daughter.
موري-ساما، تلك هي الابنة الكبرى، كازوي-سان
She currently manages an art gallery.
تدير معرضاً فنّياً في الوقت الراهن
Imamura. Who might this be?
إيمامورا، من هذا الشخص؟
Yes, this is Mori-sama, a friend of your father's.
أجل، إنّه موري-ساما، أحد أصدقاء أبيك
How do you do?
سُررت بلقائك
Oh, Father's friend?
صديقٌ لأبي؟
Imamura Kazue (30) Eldest daughter
(إيتشيكاوا كازوي (30 الابنة الكبرى لعائلة إيتشيكاوا
Isn't it a bother, being forced to attend a gathering like this?
ألا يُثقل عليك حضور مناسبات كهذه؟
No, not at all! I came with my family...
...البتّة! أتيتُ مع عائلتي
...and we're having a great time!
ونحن نستمتع بوقتنا
Oh, Sister!
!عجباً، أختاه
I didn't think you'd actually come.
لم أتوقّع أنّك ستأتين حقّاً
Of course I would attend.
بالطبع سآتي
I'm the next in line in the Ichikawa family.
فأنا التالية في الترتيب في عائلة إيتشيكاوا
I wonder. I somehow doubt
أتساءل حول ذلك
Ichikawa Mizue (27) Second daughter
(27) إيتشيكاوا ميزوي الابنة الثانية لعائلة إيتشيكاوا
Father would give everything to you.
فلا أظنّ أبي يوافقك الرأي
You did act selfishly and leave home after you argued with him.
تصرّفتِ بأنانيّة، وتركتِ البيت بعدما تشاجرتِ معه
Who're you to talk?
لا يحقّ لكِ الكلام
You got married right away because you were sick of seeing his face!
فألم تتزوّجي سريعاً لأنّك سئمتِ من رؤية وجهه؟
That reminds me, I hear your art gallery is being sued
بالمناسبة، سمعت أنّ معرضك الفنّي يتعرض للمقاضاة
for selling forgeries or something like that!
لبيعك قطعاً مزيّفة وما شابه
What?!
ماذا؟
One is as bad as the other...
الواحدة أطلح من الأخرى
"Both daughters have terrible personalities."
"كلتا الابنتين تعانيان من شخصيّة سيّئة"
"Cave (a wine storeroom)"
(الكهف (مخزن نبيذ
It's Kazue-san!
!إنّها كازوي-سان
A syringe! What is she planning to do?!
!إبرة حقن! ما الذي تنوي فعله؟
What's in it?!
!ما بداخلها؟
Oh no!
!تبّاً
Chloroform...
...كلوروفورم
Where could Conan-kun have gone off to?
أين ذهب كونان-كن يا ترى؟
I thank you for gathering here on my birthday.
أقدّم لكم شكري لاجتماعكم هنا في عيد ميلادي
I intend to give up my position as company president very soon.
أنوي التنازل عن منصبي كرئيس الشركة قريباً
In other words, I'm retiring.
أي سأتقاعد
Therefore, I've decided to sell all my stock and ownership rights
لذا قرّرتُ بيع كلّ أسهمي وحقوقي في الملكيّة
to Nichiuri Industries.
لنيتشيوري للصناعة
What?!
!ماذا؟
S-Sir! What happens to us, then?!
!سـ-سيّدي الرئيس! ما الذي سيحلّ بنا إذاً؟
If you want to stay with the company,
...إذا أردتم البقاء مع الشركة، فعليكم إثبات
you'll need to prove your worth to the new administration.
كفاءتكم للإدارة الجديدة
Y-You can't be serious!
!لا-لا يُعقل
What'll you do with the money you make from selling the company?!
ما الذي ستفعله بالأموال التي !ستجنيها من بيع الشركة؟
How I use it is up to me.
كيفيّة استعمالها تعود لي
I have no intention of giving any of you a single yen.
لا نيّة لي بإعطائكم قرشاً
Not even my daughters.
حتّى ابنتيّ
Damn, I let my guard down! I gotta hurry!
!تبّاً، أهملت! عليّ الإسراع
It was probably poison she put in the wine!
!ما حقنت النبيذ به كان سمّاً على الأرجح
How does she plan to use it?!
!كيف تنوي استعماله؟
I won't object to your decision, Father.
لن أعترض على قرارك يا أبي
Nor will I.
ولا أنا
I brought out a '57 wine to celebrate this new chapter in your life!
أحضرتُ نبيذاً من سنة 57 للاحتفال بهذه الصفحة الجديدة في حياتك
It's worth even more for a wine aficionado like yourself.
يحمل قيمةً أكبر لهاوٍ للنبيذ مثلك
I'd feel bad for the wine if regular know-nothings like us drank it.
سيكون من المؤسف للنبيذ أن يشربه جاهلون بقيمته مثلنا
Here you are.
تفضّل
Oh, she's more considerate than I thought!
إنّها صالحةٌ أكثر مما توقّعت
Hey, I haven't seen Conan-kun for a while.
لم أرَ كونان-كن لفترة
Huh?
ماذا؟
Ouch!
!مؤلم
What was that?
ما هذا؟
Perfect!
!ممتاز
Success!
!نجاح
But ouch!
!لكن آخ
Ran-neechan!
!ران-نيتشان
Oh, Conan-kun!
...كونان-كن
What happened to Ichikawa-san?!
ماذا حدث لإيتشيكاوا-سان؟
He suddenly collapsed!
انهار فجأةً
President!
!سيّدي الرئيس
Well?!
ماذا إذاً؟
Father!
!أبي
Sir!
!سيّدي
Call the police!
!استدعوا الشرطة
Huh?!
ماذا؟
This is an unnatural death for now. A police examiner is needed.
،هذا موت غير طبيعيّ حالياً سنحتاج تحليل الشرطة
A glass?
كأس زجاجيّ؟
So, he collapsed immediately after drinking the wine?
انهار فور شربه للنبيذ إذاً؟
Yes.
أجل
He was murdered!
!لقد قُتل
He did have a weak heart, but one drink wouldn't have killed him!
مهما كان قلبه ضعيفاً، يستحيل أن يموت !بعد جرعة نبيذ واحدة
There was poison in the wine!
!كان هناك سمٌّ في النبيذ
Come again?! Are you suggesting I poisoned it?!
ماذا؟! أتقصدين أنّني سمّمته؟
That's the only possibility!
!هذا الاحتمال الوحيد
You're horrible!
!يا للفظاعة
Do you have a basis for your claim?
ألديك أساس لادّعائك؟
Dr. Okano knows about our father's condition!
!يعرف الطبيب أوكانو حالة أبي
It's true that he had a weak heart,
،صحيحٌ أنّ قلبه كان ضعيفاً
but something so soon and sudden is out of the question.
لكنّ حدثاً مفاجئاً كهذا غير مُحتمل
See!
!رأيتم؟
Are you still saying it was me?!
!أتقصدين أنّها أنا؟
Now, now! I'm sorry to ask, but may we inspect your belongings?
اعذريني، لكن هل يمكننا تفقّد أغراضك؟
Dr. Okano. Can you tell what's in this vial?
طبيب أوكانو، هل يمكنك معرفة ما بهذه القنّينة؟
It seems to be a muscle relaxant.
يبدو أنّه مُرخي عضلات
What would happen if this was given to Mr. Ichikawa?
ماذا يحصل إذا تجرّعه السيّد إيتشيكاوا إذاً؟
It's very dangerous even for healthy individuals.
إنّه بغاية الخطورة حتّى للأصحّاء
Given that he had a serious heart illness...
...وبما أنّه كان يعاني مرض قلبٍ عضال
There's no question she was the one who poisoned the wine.
،لا شكّ أنّها هي من أضافت السمّ للنبيذ
But just who attacked me?!
لكن من الذي هاجمني؟
Do you have any idea as to Kazue-san's motive?
ألديكِ فكرة عن دافع كازوي-سان؟
Her art gallery was in quite a lot of debt.
،كان معرضها الفنّي غارقاً في الديون
Maybe she was after the inheritance?
فلعلّها كانت تسعى للميراث
He declared he wouldn't even leave his own daughters a single yen.
أعلن أنّه لن يسلّم ولو قرشاً واحداً لابنتيه
How dumb.
يا للحماقة
We'd still get our legally-secured portions, no matter what he said.
سنتلقّى حصصنا القانونيّة مهما قال
Even if he said nothing, we'd still get a percentage of it.
حتّى لو بقي صامتاً، سنأخذ نسبةً منه
Did the younger sister attack me?!
هل كانت هذه الأخت الصغيرة من هاجمتني؟
If she knew about her sister's plan
،إذا اكتشفت خطّة أختها
and locked me up to keep me from getting in her way...
...واحتجزتني كيلا أعترضها
If the older sister was found guilty,
،إذا تمّ ضبط جريمة الأخت الكبيرة
the huge inheritance would be all hers!
!سيكون الميراث الكبير لها وحدها
A single key not on his keychain?
مفتاح واحد بلا سلسلة؟
Hey! Hey, hey!
!المعذرة، المعذرة
What does this key go to?
أخبرني ما هذا المفتاح؟
Oh, I think it might be the basement key.
أظنّه مفتاح القبو
How odd. He almost never went into the basement...
يا للغرابة، لم يذهب السيّد للقبو في عادته
Wait!
...أيمكن
Was it the victim, Ichikawa-san, who threw me into the basement?!
أكان من هاجمني واحتجزني في القبو !هو الضحيّة إيتشيكاوا-سان؟
If so, that means he knew the wine was poisoned when he drank it!
في تلك الحالة، فقد شرب النبيذ !مع علمه أنّه مسموم
That can't be!
!غير معقول
A video camera lens!
!عدسات كاميرا فيديو
The cord goes into the ceiling!
!السلك ممتدٌّ من السقف
Was this to record the person who killed him?!
أكان هذا لتصوير الشخص الذي قتله؟
This smell... Ichikawa-san didn't drink the wine after all!
!هذه الرائحة... لم يشرب إيتشيكاوا-سان النبيذ بالفعل
He knew the eldest daughter, Kazue-san, had tampered with the wine,
،عرف أنّ الابنة الكبرى كازوي-سان عبثت بالنبيذ
so he dumped it into this flowerpot!
!فسكب النبيذ في هذا الأصيص
Then he pretended to drink it and writhe in pain...
!ثمّ تظاهر بشربه وسقوطه ألماً
...to see how both daughters reacted!
!لرؤية ردّة فعل الابنتين
But there's no doubt that he really was poisoned.
لكن لا شكّ بأنّه سُمّم فعلاً
I don't get it! How did he ingest the poison?!
!لا أفهم! كيف تجرّع السمّ؟
Damn kid, scampering around everywhere...
...يا إلهي، يتجوّل في المكان
Maybe they gave him poison in a capsule or something, not wine?
،ماذا لو تلقّى السمّ عبر كبسولة وليس من النبيذ؟
No, the time doesn't add up.
كلا، ذلك غير ممكن من ناحية الوقت
It's no good!
لا جدوى
No one could've given him the poison in front of everyone else!
يستحيل أنّ أحداً سمّمه !على مرأى من الجميع
Given?
تلقّى؟
That's it! Only that person could've done it!
وجدتُها! من كان قادراً على ذلك !كان ذاك الشخص فقط
You damn kid, sneaking into a place like this!
!أيّها الشقيّ! تتسلّل لمكانٍ كهذا؟
What the--?!
!ماذا؟
Now, then!
حسناً إذاً
I'm a pathetic personal physician. I couldn't save him...
...أنا طبيب شخصيّ فاشل، لم أستطع إنقاذه
Don't say that! It's not your fault!
!لا تقل ذلك! لم تكن غلطتك
I'm sorry to keep you all waiting.
أعتذر على الإطالة يا سادة
I've finally figured out the truth behind this incident,
اكتشفتُ حقيقة هذه القضيّة أخيراً
so please gather in the business room.
فاجتمعوا في غرفة الأعمال من فضلكم
What do you mean by "the truth," Mori-kun?
ما قصدك بأنّك اكتشفت الحقيقة يا موري-كن؟
Indeed, I have no doubt that Kazue-san poisoned the wine.
من الصحيح أنّ كازوي-سان سمّمت النبيذ
However, Ichikawa-san never drank it.
لكن لم يشربه إيتشيكاوا-سان قطّ
Not even a sip.
ولا حتى رشفة واحدة
What do you mean?
ما قصدك؟
He pretended to drink, but dumped it in the flowerpot by the window.
تظاهر بشربه، وسكبه في الأصيص عند النافذة
Then it was his heart?
أكان السبب قلبه إذاً؟
No. He died of a poison-induced heart attack. I'm certain of it.
،كلا، مات من نوبة قلبيّة أثارها سمّ لا شكّ في ذلك
What kind of nonsense is this?! My sister obviously killed him!
ما الهراء الذي تتفوّه به؟! كانت أختي !من قتلته بوضوح
I guess he just couldn't accept death normally,
أعتقد أنّه لم يتقبّل الموت بشكلٍ طبيعيّ
even though he trusted you two until the very last moment...
رغم أنّه وثق بكما حتّى النهاية
But didn't he hire you to investigate because he didn't trust them?
لكن ألم يعيّنك للتحرّي لأنّه لم يثق بهما؟
He wanted to trust them. So he tested them.
أراد الوثوق بهما، لذا اختبرهما
Ran. Play the video tape.
ران، شغّلي شريط التسجيل
Okay.
حاضر
What is this?!
ما هذا؟
This was all set up by Ichikawa-san.
كلّ هذا من إعداد إيتشيكاوا-سان
He probably planned to pretend to collapse from his heart illness
،نوى التظاهر بالانهيار من مرض قلبه غالباً
and then check later on the tape to see how both daughters reacted.
ثمّ التحقّق لاحقاً من شريط التسجيل لرؤية ردّة فعليكما
But the plan changed somewhat
لكن تغيّرت خطّته
when he learned Kazue-san was planning to kill him.
عندما علم أنّ ابنته الكبرى كازوي-سان قد خطّطت لقتله
So that's...
...عندها
So that's when he decided to pretend to drink the poisoned wine.
عندها تظاهر بشرب النبيذ المسموم
Wait, hold on. Wasn't it poison that caused his death?
انتظر، انتظر قليلاً! ألم يكن السمّ سبب موته؟
That, we can be certain of.
لا شكّ في ذلك
But it wasn't added to his wine or food.
لكنّه لم يُضف للنبيذ أو طعامه
It was given to him with a more direct method.
بل تلقّاه بطريقة مباشرة أكثر
Hold on now. I'm not sure anyone had enough time to do that.
انتظر، لا أظنّ أنّ أحداً امتلك وقتاً كافياً لفعل ذلك
Yeah! Everyone was watching!
!صحيح! كان الجميع يشاهدون
Yes. The killer openly gave him the poison while everyone watched.
أجل، سمّم القاتل إيتشيكاوا-سان أمام أنظار الجميع
Ran. Pause the tape.
ران، أوقفي الشريط
Okay.
حسناً
You don't mean--?!
!أيمكن؟
Yes.
أجل
Dr. Okano.
طبيب أوكانو
You could've given him a shot of poison instead of a heart stimulant.
كان بمقدورك حقنه بسمٍّ على أساس أنّه محفز قلب
You knew of Ichikawa-san's plan, did you not?
كنت محيطاً بخطّة إيتشيكاوا-سان، أليس كذلك؟
When you think about it,
،بالتفكير في الأمر
he would've required his doctor's help to put on the act.
كان ليحتاج مساعدة طبيبه لإتمام تمثيله
Otherwise, you would've realized he was faking right away.
وإلّا كنتَ ستدرك أنّه يتظاهر فوراً
Ichikawa-san confided his plan to you alone.
ائتمنك إيتشيكاوا-سان على خطّته وحدك
I don't know what that plan was,
،لا أدري ما كانت الخطّة بالضبط
but you decided to use it as a chance to murder him.
لكنّك قرّرت استغلالها والإقدام على قتله
Everyone knew he had a weak heart.
كان الجميع يعرفون ضعف قلبه
So no one would doubt his personal physician's diagnosis.
فلن يشكّ أحدٌ في طبيبه الشخصيّ
But why?! He has nothing to do with the inheritance, right?!
لكن لمَ؟ لا علاقة له بالميراث، أليس كذلك؟
The most likely possibility is revenge.
الدافع الذي يتراءى لي هو الانتقام
As his personal doctor,
،بصفتك طبيبه الشخصيّ
there was no need to dirty your own hands to kill him.
لم تكن هناك حاجة لتلويث يديك بقتله
If you had told him his condition wasn't serious, given how he was,
،إذا أخبرته أنّ حالته لم تكن خطرة، فبالنظر لشخصيّته
he would've kept pushing himself, hastening his death.
كان سيضغط على نفسه ولن يتقاعد، مما سيعجّل وفاته
The fact you instead took direct action...
...إقدامك على فعلةٍ مباشرة يعني أنّك
I despised him.
أبغضتُه
To that extent.
لذاك الحدّ
The president--no, Ichikawa Kotaro--killed my father.
قتل الرئيس، بل إيتشيكاوا كوتارو، أبي
Ichikawa and my father were partners when the business started.
كان أبي وإيتشيكاوا شريكين عندما تأسّست شركتُهما
It happened thirty years ago.
حدث ذلك قبل 30 عاماً
The venture business they started together was a great success.
حقّقت مجازفتهما التجارية نجاحاً كبيراً
But then he backstabbed my father and kicked him out
لكنّ هذا الرجل خان أبي وطرده
without even a yen to his name.
دون إعطائه ينّاً واحداً
Family life was miserable after that.
كانت حياتي العائلية تعيسةً بعدها
He would always utter complaints to me, just a little kid.
كان يتشكّى لي، ابنه الصغير، دوماً
In the end, my mother passed away before I entered middle school,
في النهاية، تُوفيت أمّي قبل دخولي المدرسة المتوسّطة
and my father hastened his own death.
وعجّل أبي موته
Then, after I became a doctor, this man appeared before me.
عندها، ظهر هذا الرجل أمامي بعدما أصبحتُ طبيباً
He never realized who I was.
لم يدرك من كنت
But when he told me about his plan to test his daughters' loyalty,
لكن عندما أخبرني بخطّته ،في اختبار ولاء ابنتيه
I suddenly made up my mind.
حسمتُ قراري
A horrible backstabber like him, testing the loyalty of others...
كبير خونةٍ مثله يختبر ولاء الآخرين؟
I had to make him pay...
...لم أستطع مسامحته
I had to make him pay!
!لم أستطع مسامحته
I'm going to be busy now!
!حسناً، سأكون مشغولةً الآن
I need to organize the things Father left me!
!عليّ تنظيم الأشياء التي تركها أبي
Madam!
!سيّدتي
Madam! About that...
...سيّدتي، بخصوص ذلك
Your father said in his will that if something should happen to him,
ذكر سيّدي في وصيّته أنّه ،في حال أُصيب بمكروه
everything should be donated away.
فسيتمّ التبرّع بكلّ شيء
Don't be stupid! I won't allow any such thing!
!لا تعبث معي! لن أسمح بشيءٍ كهذا
But he did have the will written in the presence of an attorney...
...لكنّه كتب الوصيّة في حضرة محامٍ
Listen. There's something called a "legally-secured portion."
اسمع، هناك ما يُسمّى بالحصص المفروضة قانونياً
I insist on receiving what I deserve!
!سأحصل على ما هو من حقّي
Mizue-san.
ميزوي-سان
What is it?
ما الأمر؟
I hear you disposed of your father's stock certificates on your own.
سمعتُ أنّك تخلّصتِ من شهادات أسهم والدك بنفسك
I'm told the board of directors is charging you with embezzlement.
وصلني أنّ مجلس الإدارة سيقاضيك بالاختلاس
No way! It's not true! It's not true!
!لا يمكن! لا يمكن! لا يمكن
In the end, Ichikawa-san's daughters
في النهاية، لم تحصل أيّ من ابنتي إيتشيكاوا-سان
don't even get one yen of his inheritance...
على ينٍّ من ميراثه حتّى
H-Hey! What's gonna happen to this house?!
انتظروا! ما الذي سيحلّ بهذا المنزل؟
What do you mean? It's going to be donated to someone.
ما قصدك؟ سيتمّ التبرّع به لأحدٍ بالتأكيد
Then what happens to my pay?!
!ماذا سيحلّ بأجري إذاً؟
You got a million yen already!
!حصلت على مليون ينٍّ سلفاً
What about the other million?!
!ماذا عن المليون الأخرى؟
Just forget about it?
انسَها
No!
!كلا
H-Hold on!
!أ-أنت
What do you think you're doing?
ما الذي تفعله؟
And, just by chance yet again, you're here too, Mori-kun?!
...وهل صادف هذه المرّة أيضاً
P-Please don't shout, Inspector. My hangover is killing me...
!لا-لا تصرخ رجاءً حضرة المفتّش ...أعاني آثار الثمل ورأسي يوجعني
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
The Famous Potter Murder Case (Part 1).
جريمة قتل الفخّاري الشهير (الجزء الأوّل)
Next Conan's hint with Detective Takagi:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة، معكم الضابط تاكاغي
Marbles.
كور رخاميّة
Next episode is about pottery.
(قضيّة الحلقة القادمة عن الفخّار! (ياكيمونو
I like my meat medium rare.
أحبّ الشوي
We're firing clay, not grilling meat.
ذلك "ياكينيكو" يا تاكاغي-كن